Guide to the Robert J. Corry Papers, 1953-2001 UA.90.F59
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Robert J. Corry Papers
1953-2001
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Corry, Robert J.
UA.90.F59
8.75 Linear Feet (8 boxes)
Robert J. Corry was an influential pancreatic transplant surgeon who came to the University of Pittsburgh from the University of Iowa in 1994. He was a member of more than 30 professional societies and organizations, and served as president the United Network for Organ Sharing from 1989 to 1990. This collection spans the professional career of Robert Corry, focusing heavily on Corry's research and publications, although presentations and conference proceedings are also abundant.
Biography
Robert J. Corry, a Cleveland native, began his career at Yale University, where he graduated magna cum laude in 1957. He then enrolled at Johns Hopkins University, graduating in 1961. After completing an internship in pediatrics and surgery at John Hopkins in 1963, Corry completed a residency and fellowship in surgery at the Peter Bent Brigham Hospital and Massachusetts General Hospital at Harvard University. His academic career began at Harvard in 1968, where he was appointed assistant professor of surgery in 1972.
In 1973, Corry went to the University of Iowa Hospitals and Clinics, where he joined the faculty of the University of Iowa College of Medicine as associate professor of surgery and became director of transplantation at the University of Iowa Hospitals and Clinics and the VA Medical Center, Iowa City. In 1976, he was promoted to professor of surgery and in 1982, chief of surgery. He held both of these positions until he was recruited in 1994 by UPMC to head the pancreatic transplant program. From 1999 to 2000, he was one of four vice presidents of the medical staff at UPMC Presbyterian.
Robert J. Corry performed the first combined liver and pancreas excision from a single donor and transplanted the organs into two recipients. He performed more than 350 pancreas transplantations, 180 kidney transplants and 50 liver transplants. He was a member of more than 30 professional societies and organizations, including the presidency of American Society of Transplant Surgeons (1986-87). He also served as president the United Network for Organ Sharing (1989-1990). From 1995 to his death on 11 February 2002, Corry also served on the board of directors for the Pittsburgh chapter of the Transplant Recipients International Organization.
Corry's research and clinical interests included exploring methods to control organ rejection and induce tolerance, identifying ways to expand the donor pool, such as using organs from older donors, and working to develop policies for broader sharing of pancreases within the United States.
Scope and Content Notes
The collection spans the professional career of Robert J. Corry, from the beginning of his collegiate education at Yale in 1953 until his death in early 2002. It focuses heavily on Corry's research and publications, although presentations and conference proceedings are also abundant. The collection includes correspondence, research notes and materials, publications, presentation materials, and photographs and slides.
Arrangement
Additional notes are found at the series level. The collection has been arranged into nine series:
Series I. Publications, 1960-2001
Series II. Books and Chapters
Series III. Talks
Series IV. Research
Series V. Grants
Series VI. Professional Activities
Series VII. Administrative
Series VIII. Education
Series IX. Media
Access Restrictions
Some materials in Series VII are restricted to protect privacy. For questions about conditions of access, contact the University Archivist.
Acqisition Information
Gift of Robert J. Corry estate in 2002.
Previous Citation
Robert J. Corry Papers, 1953-2001, UA.90.F59, University Archives, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Health and medicine; University of Pittsburgh; Faculty papers; Boston (Mass.); Iowa City (Iowa); Pittsburgh (Pa.); Pancreas -- Surgery; Transplant surgeons; Transplantation of organs, tissues, etc. -- United States; American Society of Transplant Surgeons; Corry, Robert J.; Harvard University; Massachusetts General Hospital; Peter Bent Brigham Hospital; University of Iowa. College of Medicine; University of Iowa. Hospitals and Clinics; University of Pittsburgh. School of Medicine; UNOS (Organization); UPMC Presbyterian Hospital
- Publications, 1960-2001; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series contains a chronological arrangement of articles published in various periodicals, authored or co-authored by Robert Corry. Individual articles are contained in each folder, and in some cases, additional materials such as correspondence, drafts, and research articles are also included in the folder. The first several words of each article title are indicated in the following folder list.
  - Publications, Partial Listing (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hyaluronidase Activity of the Urine following Pitressin injection, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Improvement of therapy for congenital jejunoileal atresia, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Massive Upper-gastrointestinal tract hemorrhage, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Umbilical cord cannviation in portal system disease, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Auxiliary partial liver transplantation in the dog, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Massive retroperitoneal adrenal hemorrhage, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Erosions of the Cecum: a cause of massive hemorrhage, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Auxiliary Partial liver transplantation, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Surgical treatment of acute necrotizing pancreatitis, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Transplantation of other organs, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Renal transplant survival, the HLA system, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Heart transplantation in Congenic strains of mice, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Primarily vascularized allografts of hearts in mice, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Replantation of severed fingers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Effect of HLA haplotype matching on renal transplantation, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Immunological enhancement of primarily vascualrized rat heart, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Survival of cardiac xenografts, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Overview of transplantation, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Binding of thiopental to plasma protein, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Liver disease in renal transplant patients, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Trephine air drill, bronchial brush, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The family meeting...informed consent, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The impact of Australian antigenemia on patient survival, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Effect of prospective HLA haplogype matching, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Active enhancement of donor strain skin, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Glimpse into the future: Surgery, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Prolongation of survival of rat parathyroid allografts, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Brief glimpses into the future of transplantation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Effect of RBC transfusion, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Survival of cadaver kidneys, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Influence of blood transfusion, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Renal transplantation in Iowa, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Feasibility of HLA halotype matching, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Open Forum: Kidney preservation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - "Old Papers", 1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Matched cadaver kidneys near live graft success rate, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Ectopic pregnancy in kidney transplant patients, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Critical comparison of renal transplant, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Immunological enhancement of rat small intestinal allografts, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Psychiatric illness and human renal transplantation, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Technic for lengthening the right renal brain, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Choline acetltransferase activity, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Major factors affecting cadavers renal transplant outcome, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Renal transplantation at the University of Iowa, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Critical comparison of cold storage and dynamic perfusion, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Pulmonary infections, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Management of Surgical gastrointestinal complications, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Effect of blood transfusions on cadaver, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Effect of blood transfusions on survival, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Improving Graft and patient survival rates, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Obesity in end-stage renal disease, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Transfusion and renal allograft survival, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Pretreatment of cadaver donor, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Surgical management of complications of vascular access, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Cytomegalovirus as a cause of cecal ulcer, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Hemosiderosis without cirrhosis, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Experience with live donor nephrectomy, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Effect of timing of administration and quality of blood transfusion, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Duct drainage, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Rehabilitation and the transplant patient, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Prolongation of mouse heart allograft, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Combined effect of recipient blood transfusion, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Improving survival rates, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Pretibial rash in legionella pneumophila, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Effect of prospective matching, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Current results and expectations, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Ethical dilemmas in transplantation, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - A two-year trial of prospective HLA-DR matching, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Prospective HLA-DR matching, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Organization of a renal transplant service, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Cytomegalovirus Cecal erosion, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Effect of blood transfusion on immune responses, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Is recipient priming with graft foreign..., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Gastrointesinal Bleeding, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Salvage of external shunt, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Primarily vascularized mouse heart, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Pelvic hemodynamice and male sexual impotence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Feasibility of optimal HLA-DR matching, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Question/Answer, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Effect of Donor blood transfusion on allograft survival, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Effect of DR matching on rejection, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Decapsulation of the renal transplant, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Transfer of Murine (MV infection), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Factors influencing male sexual impotence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Optimal preservation of cadaver kidney, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Prolonged allograft and xenograft survival, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Transmission of hepatitis B, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Long-term result of conservative surgical management, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Abrogation of second-set rejection, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Colorectal perforation, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Stenosis of the iliac artery, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Prolonged heart allograft survival, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Management of the infected hemodialysis, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Third Kidney transplant, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Arterial embolization, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Transplant and dialysis, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Fibromuscular Dysplasia, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Suppressor cell induction, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Transfusion reactions, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Successful DR incompatible cadaver kidney, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Ambulatory peritoneal dialysis, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Effect of HLA A and B matching, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Effect of Cyclosporine, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Iowa update of organ donation and transplantation, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Splenectomy aborgates, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Effect of peripheral blood components, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Failure of cyclosporine to prevent in vito T cell, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Prolonged Heart allograft survival, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Evaluation of techniques of controlling exocrine drainage, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Oxygen free radical induced damage in kidneys, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Effect of Allopurinol on kidneys, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Adverse effect of cyclosporine introduction, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Stroke in renal transplant recipients, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Cyclosporine use in early graft disfunction, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Surgical treatment of diabetic nephropathy, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Function of organs obtained from pancreas donors, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Cadaver kidney preservation, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Erythromytcin and cyclosporine, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - On Organ transplantation, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Transplantation of the intact pancreas organ, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Changes in Anti-HLA antibody levels, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Duodenocystostomty for exocrine pancreatic drainage, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Aseptic meningitis, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Metabolic effects of urinary diversion of the exocrine, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Case against proliferation of organ transplant centers, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Critical analysis of mortality and graft loss, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Metabolic monitoring in renal-pancreatic transplants, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Cyclosporine to azathioprine conversion, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - University of Iowa Experience in Pancreatic Transplantation, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Prolonged mouse heart allograft survival, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Results of the conversion from cyclosporine, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Evolution of technique, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Techniques of simultaneous renal pancreatoduodenal, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Duodenopanceratectomy, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Incidence and Morbidity of cytomegalovirus, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Public Policy and Organ Distribution, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Improving Patient and Graft Survival Rates, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Blood Transfusions: A randomized comparison, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Recommendations, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Nosocomial aseptic meningitis, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Pancreatic Transplant Imaging, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Pancreas Donor Criteria, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Combined Pancrease-kidney transplantation, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Vascularized Pancreatic transplantation, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Peroperative Transfusions, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Pancreatic transplants, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Vascularized Pancreas transplantation, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Post-operative complications, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Improved functional status of patients, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Comparison of cholesterol levels, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Application of magnetic resonance, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Increased frequency of post-transplant lymphomas, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Elevation of vascular resistance in the rat pancreas, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Are DST, Allograft-induced suppressor cells donor specific?, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Prolongation of Allograft and Xenograft survival, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Interleukin-2 Assay in Serum and Urine, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Diagnosis of Pancreatic rejection, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Comparison of fasting serum cholesterol levels, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Effects of donor size, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Combined hepatic and pancreaticoduodenal, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Appearance of type II diabetes, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Increased frequency of post-transplant lymphomas, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Combined retrieval of liver and pancreas grafts, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Function of simultaneous kidney and pancreas transplants, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Function of pancreas allografts, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Recent advances in whole organ...address, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Successful treatment of high-output fistula, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Diagnosis of pancreas transplant rejection, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Arterial homograft use, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Subcutaneous mycobacteriosis, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Osteomyelitis of the foot, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Physiologic studies of urinary..., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Atheromatous embolization, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Pneumonia incidence in renal transplantation, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Pancreatic allograft thrombosis, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Thrombosis in human pancreatic transplantation, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Quality of life in diabetic recipients of kidney transplants, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Vascular response to cyclosporine, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Elimination of acute GVHD, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Lower urinary tract complications presentat6ion, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Successful combined liver, pancreas allograft, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Combined experience with immediate pancreas re-transplantation, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Pancreas and renal disfunction, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Status report on pancreas transplantation, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pancreas transplantation, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Review of the effect of successful pancreas transplantation, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Status report on pancreas transplantation, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Lower urinary tract complications, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Systematic...sepsis, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Life quality of pancreatic transplant recipients, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Effect of blood transfusions, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Present status of whole-organ pancreas transplantation, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Long-term lipid metabolism, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Update on pancreas transplantation, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Impact of pancreas transplantation on quality of life, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Markers for pancreatic allograft rejection, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Pancreas transplantation, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Draft paper: MMF v. AZA, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Regulation of Immune reactivity, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Simultaneous pancreas, kidney, bone marrow transplantation, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Splemic induced to lerance and correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Pancreas transplantation without antibody induction, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Fine-needle aspiration biopsy, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Enteric drainage, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Advantages for the rapid en block technique, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Combined simultaneous kidney, bone marrow, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Spontaneous arterio-enteric fistula and en-bloc pancreas, 1996? (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Simultaneous kidney-pancreas transplantation, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Enteric drained pancreas transplants, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Rapid en block technique, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Augmentation of chimerism with preoperative donor bone marrow, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Pancreas transplantation with enteric drainage, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Three years of follow-up of bone marrow augmented..., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Treatment of isolated pancreatic islets, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - En bloc pancreas and kidney transplantations, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Perioperative donor bone marrow infusion, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - An attempt to reverse diabetes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Comparison of azxthioprine and mycophenolate, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Serum lipase as a marker, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Surgical complications in 123 consecutive..., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Tacrolimus without antilymphocyte induction, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Pancreas transplantation, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Long-term results, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Potential use of marginal donors, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Methods of organ procurement, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Strategies to expand the donor pool, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - High-risk donors, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Simultaneous administration of adjuvant donor bone marrow, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Interesting intraoperative decisions, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Simultaneous pancreas-kidney transplantation, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Results of pancreas transplantation, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Renal allograft rejection, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Logistics and techniques for procurement..., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Consensus statement on the live organ donor, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Steroid withdrawal, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Long-term lipid metabolism, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Kidney transplantation with bone marrow augmentation, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Comparison of enteric versus bladder drainage, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Books and Chapters, II.
  This series contains both published and unpublished articles and chapters, authored or co-authored by Corry, that were to be included in monographs. The series is arranged in rough chronological order. Information about each chapter in this series may include drafts, reprints, notes, and correspondence.
  - New possibilities for organ allografting in the mouse, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Update on pancreas transplantation for "Advances in Surgery", undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Attempt to induce tolerance, proceedings of the fourth international dendritic cell meeting, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Current opinion in organ transplantation, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Instructions - book chapter, Corry, Shapiro, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - The mesetery and the omentum, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Shock, undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Gastrointestinal hemorrhage, chapter 22, Syn. In Surgery, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Legionnaires disease, undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Surgical complications, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Transplantation, undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Gastrointestinal hemorrhage, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Renal transplantation case studies, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Status of transplantation of human organs, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Role of renal afferent nerves, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Manipulation of the immune response for "transplant surgery", 1987 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Sandimmune for LRD Monograph, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Whole organ pancreas transplantation, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Pancreatico-duodenal transplantation, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Bowel drained pancreas transplants for Toelo-Perregra, "Rawer, Transplant", 1988 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Experience with Pancreas transplantation, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Renal and renal pancreas transplantation in Type I... for "Clinical Tx", 1988 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Experience at the University of Iowa college of medicine for International handbook of pancreases, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Pancreatic transplantation and bladder damage, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - The future of transplantation, UNOS chapter, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Diagnostic imaging in renal transplantation, for the handbook of transplantation management, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Diagnostic radiology of pancreas transplantation for the handbook of transplantation management, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Current status of hepatic transplantation (chapter), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Draft: Pancreas Transplantation, undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Draft: Kidney Transplantation with Bone marrow (Box 2, Folder 99)